rockstarleadmachine.com 2017-02-02

# Privacy Policy | The RockStar Lead Machine

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name and e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by contacting us at http://offlinerockstaracademy.com/support/

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at http://offlinerockstaracademy.com/support/

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, 2ROCKSTARS has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting 2ROCKSTARS, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of 2ROCKSTARS then you may contact us at http://offlinerockstaracademy.com/support/
